♪ The Big Bang Theory 9x23 ♪
The Line Substitution Solution
Original Ai
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Raj:)Did you guys see there's
an Avengers screening?
(Raj:)Joss Whedon's gonna show
some deleted scenes
(Raj:)and do a question
and answer session.
(Sheldon:)Oh, well, I have
a few questions for him
about the last Avengers movie...
and a whole lot of answers.
(Leonard:)When's the screening?
(Raj:)Uh, it's tonight, but it's
first-come, first-served,
(Raj:)so we should probably get
there early and wait in line.
Let's do it. (chuckles)
(Leonard:)Penny's busy with my mother,
so I'm in.
(Sheldon:)Oh, bad news.
(Sheldon:)Amy's making me go shopping
with her later,
(Sheldon:)so looks like none of us can go.
(Leonard:)You do realize we're allowed
to have fun without you?
(Howard:)In fact, that's usually
the trick to it.
(Howard:)What time do we
need to get there?
Uh, I'd say by 3:00.
(Sheldon:)You're really going without me?
(Leonard:)It's not a big deal.
(Leonard:)Go shopping with Amy,
(Leonard:)and we'll save
a spot in line for you.
(Sheldon:)You don't have the authority
to save places in the line.
(Sheldon:)If I do that, I'll be cutting.
(Leonard:)People do it all the time.
(Sheldon:)You know the golden rule
of line etiquette:
“No cuts, no buts,
no coconuts.”